http://www.asesystems.com/privacy/

Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
AseSystems Privacy Policy
Ase Systems respects your privacy.
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Ase Systems.
Credit card details
Ase Systems will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Ase Systems.
External Sites.
Ase Systems is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Ase Systems to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Ase Systems does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Ase Systems and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Ase Systems have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
Case Studies Be sure to check out our recent material handling case studies.
Contact Us
If you would like to send an attachment Click Here
Please Add Me To Your Mail List
The capital of Japan?
Input this code:
